
const qBank = [
  
  {
    question:
      'How do we say "HI" in French?   ',
    answers: ["Salut", "au revoir", "Merci", "Bienvenue"],
    correct: "Salut",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:
      'How do we say "BYE" in French?',
    answers: ["Salut", "au revoir", "Merci", "Bienvenue"],
    correct: "au revoir",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "Thankyou" in French?',
    answers: ["Salut", "au revoir", "Merci", "Bienvenue"],
    correct: "Merci",
    questionId: "267908"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Welcome" in French?',
    answers: ["Salut", "au revoir", "Merci", "Bienvenue"],
    correct: "Bienvenue",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Sorry" in French?',
    answers: ["aliments", "désolé", "l'eau", "dormir"],
    correct: "désolé",
    questionId: "496293"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "Food" in French?',
    answers: ["aliments", "désolé", "l'eau", "dormir"],
    correct: "aliments",
    questionId: "588909"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "Water" in French?',
    answers: ["aliments", "désolé", "l'eau", "dormir"],
    correct: "l'eau",
    questionId: "648452"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Sleep" in French?',
    answers: ["aliments", "désolé", "l'eau", "dormir"],
    correct: "dormir",
    questionId: "786649"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "Nice to meet you" in French?',
    answers: ["Aidez-moi", "Ravi de vous rencontrer", "Oui", "je t'aime"],
    correct: "Ravi de vous rencontrer",
    questionId: "839754"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "Help" in French?',
    answers: ["Aidez-moi", "Ravi de vous rencontrer", "Oui", "je t'aime"],
    correct: "Aidez-moi",
    questionId: "98390"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "YES" in French?',
    answers: ["Aidez-moi", "Ravi de vous rencontrer", "Oui", "je t'aime"],
    correct: "Oui",
    questionId: "1071006"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "NO" in French?',
    answers: ["Aidez-moi", "NON", "Oui", "je t'aime"],
    correct: "NON",
    questionId: "1174154"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "glass" in French?',
    answers: ["verre", "pluie", "Skin", "temps"],
    correct: "verre",
    questionId: "1226535"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Rain" in French?',
    answers:  ["verre", "pluie", "Skin", "temps"],
    correct: "pluie",
    questionId: "1310938"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Sun" in French?',
    answers:  ["verre", "pluie", "Skin", "temps"],
    correct: "Skin",
    questionId: "1436873"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Time" in French?',
    answers: ["verre", "pluie", "Skin", "temps"],
    correct: "temps",
    questionId: "1515110"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Light" in French?',
    answers: ["argent", "pluie", "lumière", "verre"],
    correct: "lumière",
    questionId: "1642728"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "I love you" in French?',
    answers: ["je t'aime", "Ravi de vous rencontrer", "S'il vous plaît", "je m'appelle"],
    correct: "je t'aime",
    questionId: "1747256"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "Money" in French?',
    answers: ["argent", "pluie", "lumière", "verre"],
    correct: "argent",
    questionId: "1822532"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Please" in French?',
    answers:  ["je t'aime", "Ravi de vous rencontrer", "S'il vous plaît", "je m'appelle"],
    correct: "S'il vous plaît",
    questionId: "195075"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "My name is" in French?',
    answers: [" Comment tu t'appelles", "je m'appelle", "Ça va", "Ça va bien"],
    correct: "je m'appelle",
    questionId: "2019778"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "What is you name" in French?',
    answers: [" Comment tu t'appelles", "je m'appelle", "Ça va", "Ça va bien"],
    correct: " Comment tu t'appelles",
    questionId: "2134343"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "How are you" in French?',
    answers: [" Comment tu t'appelles", "je m'appelle", "Ça va", "Ça va bien"],
    correct: "Ça va",
    questionId: "2210799"
  },
  {
    question:
    'How do we say "IM fine" in French?',
    answers: [" Comment tu t'appelles", "je m'appelle", "Ça va", "Ça va bien"],
    correct: "Ça va bien",
    questionId: "2379831"
  },
  {
    question:  'How do we say "Good Morning" in French?',
    answers: ["Bonsoir", "Bonjour", "Bonne soirée", "Bonne nuit"],
    correct: "Bonjour",
    questionId: "2426418"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say " Good Evening" in French?',
    answers: ["Bonsoir", "Bonjour", "Bonne soirée", "Bonne nuit"],
    correct: "Bonsoir",
    questionId: "2510086"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Have a Good Evening" in French?',
    answers: ["Bonsoir", "Bonjour", "Bonne soirée", "Bonne nuit"],
    correct: " Bonne soirée",
    questionId: "2685745"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Good Night" in French?',
    answers:  ["Bonsoir", "Bonjour", "Bonne soirée", "Bonne nuit"],
    correct: " Bonne nuit",
    questionId: "2796884"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Monday" in French?',
    answers: ["Lundi", " Mardi", "Mercredi", "Jeudi"],
    correct: "Lundi",
    questionId: "2838900"
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the French word for "hat"?',
    answers: ["Chapeau", "Bonnet", " Écharpe", " Casque"],
    correct: "Chapeau",
    questionId: "298060"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Tuesday" in French?',
    answers:["Lundi", " Mardi", "Mercredi", "Jeudi"],
    correct: " Mardi",
    questionId: "3096579"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Wednesday" in French?',
    answers:["Lundi", " Mardi", "Mercredi", "Jeudi"],
    correct: "Mercredi",
    questionId: "3182461"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Thursday" in French?',
    answers: [
      "Jeudi",
      "Mercredi",
      "Mardi",
      "Lundi"
    ],
    correct: "Jeudi",
    questionId: "3239112"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Friday" in French?',
    answers: ["Lundi", "Vendredi", "Jeudi", "Mardi"],
    correct: "Vendredi",
    questionId: "3318503"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Saturday" in French?',
    answers: ["Mardi", "Vendredi", " Samedi", "Mercredi"],
    correct: " Samedi",
    questionId: "3410327"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Sunday" in French?',
    answers: ["Samedi", "Jeudi", "Mercredi", "Dimanche"],
    correct: "Dimanche",
    questionId: "3542596"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "car" in French?',
    answers: ["école", "voiture", "véhicule", "l'avion"],
    correct: "voiture",
    questionId: "3667517"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Hospital" in French?',
    answers: [
      "hôpital",
      "école",
      "voiture",
      "l'avion"
    ],
    correct: "hôpital",
    questionId: "3791672"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "School" in French?',
    answers: [
    "hôpital",
    "école",
    "voiture",
    "l'avion"
  ],
    correct: "école",
    questionId: "3893585"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "One" in French?',
    answers: ["quatre", "un", "trois", "deux"],
    correct: "un",
    questionId: "3913430"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Two" in French?',
    answers: ["deux", "trois", "quatre", "cinq"],
    correct: "deux",
    questionId: "4049121"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Three" in French?',
    answers: ["deux", "trois", "quatre", "cinq"],
    correct: "trois",
    questionId: "4150746"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Four" in French?',
    answers:["deux", "trois", "quatre", "cinq"],
    correct: "quatre",
    questionId: "4235063"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Five" in French?',
    answers: ["deux", "trois", "quatre", "cinq"],
    correct: "cinq",
    questionId: "4321002"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Six" in French?',
    answers: ["deux", "trois", "Six", "cinq"],
    correct: "Six",
    questionId: "4442286"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Seven" in French?',
    answers: ["sept", "trois", "Six", "cinq"],
    correct: "sept",
    questionId: "4564430"
  },
  {
    question: 'How do we say "Eight" in French?',
    answers:  ["sept", "huit", "Six", "cinq"],
    correct: "huit",
    questionId: "4630606"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Nine" in French?',
    answers:  ["sept", "huit", "neuf", "cinq"],
    correct: "neuf",
    questionId: "4795960"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Ten" in French?',
    answers: ["neuf", "huit", "sept", "dix"],
    correct: "dix",
    questionId: "4811162"
  },
  {
    question:'How do we say "Shoes" in French?',
    answers: ["Chapeau", "Bonnet", " des chaussures", " Casque"],
    correct: "des chaussures",
    questionId: "4982981"
  }
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
